[{"question":"A breadboard is","answers":{"a":"A data routing circuit","b":"Used to design or test electronic circuits","c":"A code-converting circuit","d":"A temporary binary storage area"},"correctAnswer":"b"},
{"question":"What is the gap that separates two sides of the breadboard called?","answers":{"a":"The dip","b":"The rail","c":"The switch","d":"The ravine"},"correctAnswer":"d"},
{"question":"Similarity between PCB and Bread board is","answers":{"a":"Both allow to design temporary circuits.","b":"Both can be used for solderless components.","c":"Complex circuits can be designed on both.","d":"Both can handle high current."},"correctAnswer":"c"},
{"question":"The conductive metal strips on a breadboard","answers":{"a":"Contain bus strips commonly used for power connections.","b":"Provide socket strips in the build area to hold components.","c":"Are conductive with low resistance.","d":"All of the above"},"correctAnswer":"d"},
{"question":"When connecting bus or socket strips the jumper wires should be","answers":{"a":"Long enough to make the connection yet short enough to prevent complications.","b":"Wrapped in a coil to prevent interference with the other components.","c":"As long at the test instrumentâ€™s leads to decrease resistance.","d":"Soldered to the components to ensure conductivity."},"correctAnswer":"a"},
{"question":"Breadboards allow for prototyping an electrical circuit without the need to solder the components.","answers":{"a":"True","b":"False"},"correctAnswer":"a"},
{"question":"Components installed in parallel on a breadboard will share the same socket strip at both ends.","answers":{"a":"True","b":"False"},"correctAnswer":"a"},
{"question":"Using a breadboard helps in","answers":{"a":"Soldering different components.","b":"Checking function of circuits.","c":"Checking design of circuits.","d":"Both b and c."},"correctAnswer":"d"},
{"question":"The maximum frequency that can be handled by breadboard is","answers":{"a":"10 MHz","b":"10 GHz","c":"10 Hz","d":"10 KHz"},"correctAnswer":"d"},
{"question":"In preparing to build on a breadboard, one should","answers":{"a":"Simply look at the schematic and begin the build.","b":"Never assume the test equipment and components are functional.","c":"Ignore any burn marks as you are only experimenting on the circuit.","d":"Assume all jumper wires and connectors are intact."},"correctAnswer":"b"}]
